Javier González Bodas

02/08/1993

C/ Paulina Odiaga 41, Madrid, 28019

gonzalezbodasjavier@yahoo.es +34 695068361

Graduated in 2016 with a degree in Computer Engineering and currently working in the consulting sector. Experience in different technologies within the sector such as: Java, API, Connect and SAS as well as self-trained for personal projects on: JavaScript and Python.



Academic training

2011-2016 Degree in Computer Engineering

Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingenieros Informáticos Universidad Politécnica de Madrid

Experience

Java Analist/Developer in atSistemas

May 2018 - Actually

- BBDD Scripts Development (PL/SQL).
- CRM Application Development (Java, Clarify, Eclipse).
- Control Version Tools (SVN, PVCS).

• IT Engineer in Ericsson

August 2017 - May 2018

- BBDD Scripts Development (PL/SQL).
- CRM Application Development (Java, Clarify, Eclipse).
- Control Version Tools (SVN, PVCS).

APIs RESTful Consultant in M2C Consulting & Procedures

June 2017 - August 2017

API RESTful Management and Design (IBM API Connect, Node-red).

SAS Consultant in M2C Consulting & Procedures

June 2016 - June 2017

- Process Automation (Batch, Visual Basic).
- Data Analisis and Extraction, and Reporting (Business Object ,SAS, Excel, Access).

Languages

English: First Certificate in English (FCE)

Spanish: Native

Knowledge and Aptitudes

......

Java (Amdocs Clarify)
Development environments management (Eclipse)
Relational database language (SQL, PL/SQL)
JavaScript (jQuery, React)
Web design (HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap)
Bash
Python

Social Media

Personal Page: https://javibodas.github.io

Github: https://github.com/javibodas

StackOverflow: JaviBodas **LinkedIn:** Javier González Bodas